原视频名：NASA Picks SpaceX for Artemis Human Lunar Lander Development
原作者名：NASA
视频来源：youtu.be/y-sA3R4MWjA
原视频发布日期：20210416
本字幕所有特效使用Aegisub制作，字幕制作/压制：旋火
[music]
[音乐]
原视频名：NASA Picks SpaceX for Artemis Human Lunar Lander Development
原作者名：NASA
视频来源：youtu.be/y-sA3R4MWjA
原视频发布日期：20210416
本字幕所有特效使用Aegisub制作，字幕制作/压制：旋火
原视频名：NASA Picks SpaceX for Artemis Human Lunar Lander Development
原作者名：NASA
视频来源：youtu.be/y-sA3R4MWjA
原视频发布日期：20210416
本字幕所有特效使用Aegisub制作，字幕制作/压制：旋火
原视频名：NASA Picks SpaceX for Artemis Human Lunar Lander Development
原作者名：NASA
视频来源：youtu.be/y-sA3R4MWjA
原视频发布日期：20210416
本字幕所有特效使用Aegisub制作，字幕制作/压制：旋火
NASA
在准备
把宇航员
送到月球表面
还有
火星上面
阿尔忒弥斯会使用
载人着陆系统
同时迈向
下一步
[splash]
[水花]
[music]
[音乐]
把接下来的两名
美国宇航员
送上月球
The importance of landing humans back on the Moon is we're going back in a way that is totally different.
让人类重返月球的重要性在于我们要以一种完全不同的方式回去
凯西·卢德斯
载人探索任务部主任
We've had almost sixty years of experience.
我们已经有了将近60年的经验
And we're taking every single ounce of experience we have.
而这次要把我们的每一点经验都带回去
And taking that with our international partners.
并与我们的国际合作伙伴一起
With our commercial partners.
与我们的商业合作伙伴一起
We've been working for the last year with three partners
我们在过去的一年里一直在和三个伙伴合作
NASA载人登月系统项目经理
利萨·沃森-摩根
who will help us achieve the next human mission to the Moon.
而这三个伙伴将帮助我们实现下一个载人登月任务
Because we know that this first step to the Moon will then lead us to go to Mars.
因为我们知道 登上月球的第一步将为前往火星奠定基础
And we know that the Human Landing System is one of the first steps to get us there.
而我们知道 载人着陆系统是让我们到达那里的第一步
And so we've been working with Dynetics, A Leidos Company.
所以我们一直在和Leidos的子公司Dynetics合作
We've been working with Blue Origin, who have partners Draper and Lockheed Martin and Northrop Grumman.
我们一直在与蓝色起源合作 他们的合作伙伴有德雷珀 洛克希德·马丁和诺斯罗普·格鲁曼
In addition, we've also been working with SpaceX.
此外 我们也一直在与SpaceX合作
三家公司都在为
[music]
[音乐]
制造第一个着陆器的机会竞争
这将把NASA宇航员
带回月球
This is a very very exciting time for the Human Landing System program.
对于载人着陆系统项目来说 这是一个非常非常激动人心的时刻
They've spent a lot of blood, sweat, and tears over these last couple years, getting ready for this moment.
在过去的几年里 他们花费了大量的血汗和泪水 为这一刻做好了准备
We're really excited to bring you the announcement
我们真的很高兴地为大家通告
of who NASA is going to continue to finish out the Human Landing System and take humans back to the Moon.
就是谁将为NASA继续完成载人着陆系统 并将人类带回月球
NASA has chosen SpaceX to return us to the Moon.
NASA已经选择了SpaceX将我们送回月球
I am so excited to partner with SpaceX in this fantastic endeavor for the Artemis suit of missions.
我很高兴能与SpaceX共同为阿尔忒弥斯这一梦幻般系列任务而努力
So congratulations to the SpaceX team!
所以恭喜SpaceX团队
The SpaceX design is a single-stage solution, using their Starship.
SpaceX的设计是一个单级方案 使用他们的Starship
It provides extensive volume for the crew with two airlocks and amble down mass capability.
它为乘员提供了大量的容积 以及两个气闸和缓慢下行质量的能力
The SpaceX proposal included in space propellant transfer demonstration and uncrewed test landing.
SpaceX的方案包括了在轨推进剂转移验证和无人着陆验证
So now we've selected our partner
那么现在我们已经选择了我们的合作伙伴
and for the next phase going forward, we have to make sure the testing occurs,
而对于下一阶段的发展 我们必须确保测试的发生
because we're not going to launch humans until we have a successful test.
因为在测试成功之前 我们不会进行载人发射
So we will be working
那么我们将致力于
to make sure that the design and everything that we have going forward so far is ready to go.
确保我们目前的设计和一切进展都已准备就绪
So the Human Landing System is going to allow us to be able to access different parts of the lunar surface.
那么 载人着陆系统将让我们能够到达各种各样的月球表面
But it also allows us to explore a new technology and capabilities
但这也让我们能够探讨一种新的技术和能力
that will help us when we're trying to figure out our next round of technologies to help us land on Mars
这将有助我们去搞清楚下一轮用于着陆火星的技术
or other planets out there.
或者着陆其他行星
I'd like to thank the companies for the great work this past year.
我要感谢各公司在过去一年里的出色工作
We've all learned a lot.
我们都学到了很多东西
I'd like to thank the NASA team because you have definitely risen to this challenge.
我要感谢NASA的团队 因为你们肯定已经站起来扛下了这个挑战
It is one more step and an exciting group of steps
这又是一个步骤 也是一组激动人心的步骤
that will get us to a sustainable Human Landing System to the Moon.
会让我们得到一个可持续的 前往月球的载人着陆系统
[music]
[音乐]